&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：让我们谈谈另一个特殊的价值。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let's talk about another special value.
这个看起来很奇怪，因为地球上什么是负零？
This one seems rather strange because what on Earth is a negative zero?
如果你问数学家，他们会说那是捏造的，那是不存在的，
If you ask a mathematician, they'll say that's made up, that doesn't exist,
那不是真的。
that's not a real thing.
它肯定存在于编程中，它肯定存在于IEEE754中。
It definitely exists in programming, it definitely exists in IEEE 754.
就像NaN存在于IEEE754中一样，但是数学家不知道NaN是什么意思。
Just like nan exists in IEEE 754, but a mathematician doesn't know what nan means.
那么它肯定也需要，IEEE 54如果你愿意，
Then it definitely also requires, IEEE 54 if you will,
要求存在负零。
requires there to be a negative zero.
那是什么意思？
So, what does that mean?
嗯，它本质上是零值，但符号位是开的。
Well, it's essentially the zero value, but with the sign bit on.
所以它是零的负表示。
So it is the negative representation of a zero.
现在，JavaScript的早期认为JavaScript开发人员永远不会
Now, early days of JavaScript felt that JavaScript developers would never
想要负零。
want a negative zero.
所以他们实际上竭尽全力假装它没有
And so they actually went to extreme lengths to try to pretend as if it didn't
我们会看到一大堆奇怪的东西。
exist which we're gonna see a whole bunch of weirdness.
例如，如果我将-0分配给TrendRate行1，
For example, if I have a -0 assigned to trendRate line 1,
在这里，我用三倍等于-0，我得到了真的，听起来很棒。
here and I triple equals it with -0 I get true, sounds great.
如果我把它串起来会发生什么？
What happens if I stringify it?
我将在这里使用toString方法，还有其他方法，但如果我将其字符串，
I'll use the toString method here, there's other ways, but if I stringify it,
我得0分。
I get 0.
这不太好对吧？
That's not good, right?
0，我的负号在哪里？
0, where's my negative sign?
JavaScript的早期咒语感觉就像JavaScript开发人员会认为的那样
The early incantation of JavaScript felt like JavaScript developers would think
如果你取一个-0并将其字符串化为-0，然后在字符串中得到-0，那么它就是一个bug。
that it was a bug if you took a -0 and stringified it and got -0 in the string.
感觉这对最终用户来说就像是一个bug，
It felt like that would look to the end user like a bug,
JavaScript会受到指责
and JavaScript would get blamed.
我认为现在回想起来，语言应该做正确的事情
I think in retrospect, languages should do the correct thing and
开发人员有责任做一些对用户合理的事情。
it's on developers to do something that's reasonable to users.
语言不应该介入并试图猜测它们的开发人员。
Languages should not step in and try to second guess their developers.
JavaScript中有一大堆历史上的怪异之处
And there's a bunch of the historical weirdness in JavaScript where
他们出于各种原因试图变得更可口。
they tried for various reasons to be more palatable.
我们得到自动分号插入和一个完整的，整个主机的其他东西
We get automatic semi colon insertion and a whole, whole host of other things
语言试图智胜开发者。
where the language trying to out smart the developer.
结果发现开发人员并不聪明。
And it turns out don't out smart the developer.
就让他们做他们能做的事，用合理的，连贯的
Just let them do what they can with the sensible reasonable coherent
一套工具，好吗？
set of tools, okay?
好的，所以这两根绳子对我们撒谎，顺便说一句，
Okay, so the two string lies to us and by the way,
三重等于也欺骗了我们，因为它说-0等于0。
the triple equals also lies to us, cuz it says the -0 is equal to a 0.
并且在-0中既不小于0也不大于0。
And in also -0 is neither less than 0 or greater than 0.
所以，小于和小于或等于和更大，我很抱歉，
So, the less than and the less than or equal and the greater, I'm sorry,
小于和大于具体的，
the less than and a greater than specifically,
他们说谎&凯尔·辛普森：他们都在说谎。
they lie &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: They all lie.
所以很长一段时间我们都没有一个内置的方式来确定我们是否有
So for a long time we didn't really have a built in way of determining if we had
A-0，你可以得到-0，但是你不能确定你有一个。
a -0, you could get -0s, but you couldn't determine that you had one.
在ES6之前，他们添加了一个名为object.is的实用程序，
Until ES6 they added a utility called object.is,
object.is，我喜欢把这称为四倍等于。
object.is, I like to refer to this as like the quadruple equals.
人们喜欢开玩笑说双倍等于，它允许所有这些不同
People like to joke about how double equals, it allows all these different
强制和一些东西，我们将进入一个高质量的课程。
coercions and stuff we'll get into a course of a quality in bit.
他们喜欢开玩笑说双倍相等正在改变
They like to joke about double equals is changing and
三重等于是精确的，除了几个谎言外，它是严格的。
triple equals is exact, it's strict except for a couple of lies.
好吧，如果我们不想要那些谎言，那就再加一个等号，所以
Well, if we don't want those lies let's just add another equals on, so
就像这里的第四个等号。
it's like the fourth equals here.
它根本不说谎，如果它是-0，如果它是真的，否则，它不说谎。
It doesn't lie at all, if it's a -0, if it's true and otherwise, it doesn't.
如果它是零，它给出的是真还是假，我的意思是，
And if it's a zero, it gives you true or otherwise, I mean,
假的，否则它不会。
false or otherwise it doesn't.
所以这是你唯一的选择，如果你想测试零的话。
So that's your only option, if you wanna test for the zero.
实际上，从技术上讲，有一个数学运算
Actually, there's technically a mathematical operation and
这是以后的暗示。
that's a hint for later.
有一个数学运算可以用来确定-0。
There is a mathematical operation that you can use to determine -0.
但在大多数情况下，做到这一点的最好方法是使用这个内置的检查器和
But for the most part, the best way to do this is to use this built-in checker and
顺便说一下，object.is可以用来检查姓名。
by the way, object.is can be used to check names.
虽然我会说number.是一个更有语义的工具，但是
Although I would say number.is is a more semantic tool for it, but
也可以使用object.is。
you can also use object.is.
所以现在你在问自己
So now you're asking yourself,
好吧，很好，有个奇怪的细微差别的东西，没人关心，对吧？
okay great, there's this weird nuanced thing that no one cares about, right?
谁会在乎负零呢？
Who would even care about a negative zero?
嗯，我认为它们是合法的目的，
Well, I think they are legitimate purposes,
我以前实际上在我的程序中使用过负零。
I have actually use negative zeros in my programs before.
在数学上，我们很常见的是指两个独立的实体或
Mathematically it's very common for us to refer to two separate entities or
两个分隔相同数值中的特征。
two separates characteristics in the same numeric value.
例如，数字的绝对值表示
For example, the absolute value of the number represents for
例如，某物可能移动得有多快。
example how fast something might be moving.
这个标志代表了它移动的方向。
And the sign represents what direction it's moving.
假设你在地图上有一辆小汽车，这实际上就是我所拥有的。
Say you've got a little car on a map and this is actually what I had.
我在一家公司工作，我们在那里构建了这个地图解决方案，并且
I worked in a company where we built this mapping solution, and
我们有一辆绕着地图行驶的小车。
we had this little car that moved around a map.
我需要知道这辆车是朝这个方向还是这个方向移动。
And I needed to know whether the car was moving this way or this way.
当它停止时，我让它朝哪个方向看？
What direction do I make it look when it stops?
嗯，我想让它看起来和它停下来之前的方向一样。
Well, I wanted to make it look in the same direction that it was before it stopped.
我如何确定一个数字，它是什么方向，如果是零，
How do I determine what one number, what direction it was, if at zero,
我们失去了标志？
we lose the sign?
所以负零实际上是有用的，我在游戏中使用它们
So negative zero was actually useful there, and I use those in games for
非常相似的目的。
very similar purposes.
所以我们的TrendRate，正如下面的例子所说的，是
So our trendRate, as the going example goes, is that
我可以使用这个数字的符号，有一个叫做math.sign的实用程序，
I could use the sign of this number, there's a utility called math.sign,
这应该是要告诉我们这东西是不是没有符号位。
which is supposedly gonna tell us is this thing doesn't have the sign bit or not.
这应该可以告诉我们，如果我们有一个负的零。
And that should have been able to tell us if we had a negative zero.
不幸的是，他们做了一件超级愚蠢的事情
Unfortunately, that went and did something super dumb which was that they
使math.sign返回负0和0而不是负1和1。
made math.sign return negative zero and zero instead of negative one and one.
所以你不能真正使用Math.sign来确定这一点。
So you can't really use Math.sign to determine this.
但如果你想做你自己的，
But if you wanted to make your own,
在这里，我基本上是通过修正符号方法来制作自己的。
here I'm making my own by basically fixing up the sign method.
我在检查，如果，在两个0中的一个上，这就是在第8行发生的事情。
And I'm checking if, on one of the two 0s, that's what happens on line 8.
在两个0中的一个上，
And on one of the two 0s,
如果我不是两个0中的一个，而不是我可以使用这个标志。
if I'm not one of the two 0srather than I can use the sign.
如果我是两个零中的一个，我需要使用object.is来确定我是不是-0。
If I'm one of the two zeros, I need to use object.is to figure out if I'm a -0.
所以固定的up sign方法，您会注意到第13行，
So that fixed up sign method, you'll notice down there in line 13,
当存在-0时，它返回-1。
it returns a -1 when there's a -0.
因此，另一种方法可能对我们有用，我们有一个符号方法，实际上
So yet another way that it might be useful for us to have a sign method that actually
工作，这里有一种方法，我们可以用一种有用的方式来制作一个符号方法。
works, and here's a way that we can make a sign method that works in a useful way.
有一些原因
There's some reason for
返回值中的-0，但我不认为它很有用。
the -0 thing in their return value, but I don't think it's very useful.
好的，正如我所说的趋势例子。
Okay, so the trend example as I said.
趋势示例，
The trend example,
如果我想知道什么东西在朝哪个方向移动。
if I wanted to keep track of what direction something was moving.
比如，如果这是一只股票或类似的东西，我想要跟踪，
Like if this was a stock or something like that and I wanted to keep track of,
即使它是零，它是一直在下降还是一直在上升？
even if it's at zero has it been falling or has it been going up?
例如，我想展示它的股票价格是在下降还是上升。
And I wanna show whether it's been falling or rising in it's stock price for example.
在这里，你注意到，即使我跟踪一个负零，我也可以显示它已经
Where here you notice that even if I track a negative zero I can show that it's been
在那个时候坠落。
falling at that point.
与达到零值时的上升相反。
As opposed to being rising when it gets at the zero value.
所以，负零，尽管它们看起来可能有一些细微的差别，
So, negative zeros even though they seem like they may be a little bit nuanced,
它们是语言中存在的一个值，因此，您应该了解它们，并且
they're a value that exist in the language so, you should know about them and
知道如何测试他们。
know how to test for them.
现在你知道了它们的存在，你甚至可以找到它们的用途。
And now that you know that they exist, you might even be able to find uses for them.
&gt；&gt；学生：对我来说不是那样，还是很难
&gt;&gt; Student: For me it's not that, it's still hard for
我，我宁愿定义方向与。
me, and I would rather define direction versus.
对我来说很难，没有数学价值。
For me it's hard there is no math value.
我的意思是，零对，这是一种支持它的语言。
I mean, zero zero right, it's a language that supports it.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，我理解这个观点
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, I understand that perspective and
那是完全有效的，但对我来说这听起来
that's entirely valid, but that's sounds to me
就像有人说我根本不在乎负数。
like when somebody says I don't care about negative numbers at all.
我只有一些有绝对值的数字，
I just have numbers that have absolute values,
我用的是无符号整数什么的。
I used unsigned integers or something.
有符号的数字是一种东西，数学中也有一种东西，所以
Signed numbers are a thing and there a thing in math, so
如果数学中有东西，那么负零也是一个有用的东西。
if there's a thing in math then a negative zero is also a thing that can be useful.
好的，那么这些特殊的值，它们将出现在我们的程序中，
Okay, so those special values, they're gonna occur in our programs,
并且对我们程序中可能存在的类型和价值有敏锐的意识。
and having an acute awareness of types and the values that can exist in our programs.
它们不仅可以帮助我们避免bug，还可以更好地使用我们的工具。
They're gonna help us not only avoid bugs, but also make better usage of our tool.
不仅可以做一些事情，还可以做一些语义上更多的事情，
Not only just be able to do something, but maybe do something more semantically,
也许可以做一些使我们的代码更易读或更容易理解的东西。
maybe make something that makes our code more readable or more understandable.
我会争辩说，如果我使用正数或正数，它会更加一致
I would argue that it is much more consistent if I'm using positive or
在我的常规数字中为负数以指示方向，
negative in my regular numbers to indicate direction,
我不会有单独的变量来跟踪零的方向。
that I'll not have separate variable to track zeros direction.
它对我来说更加一致，我认为在代码中更具交际性，
It's much more consistent to me, and I think more communicative in code,
如果我用零的符号来表示方向。
if I use the sign of the zero to also indicate the direction.